<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

     <string name="left_network_indicators"><![CDATA[
        <style media=\"screen\" type=\"text/css\">
            body {
                color: ?android:attr/textColorPrimary ;
            }
            a:link {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
            a:visited {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
        </style>

        <h3><center><u>Moving Newtowrk Indicators to the Left</u></center></h3>

        <p>
              This is a much easier process than you think!

        </p>

        <ol>
            <li>Select the option in K-Manager to move the network indicators to the left.</li>
            <li>Tap the yellow build button at the bottom left corner of K-Manager.</li>
            <li>Install K-Klock once it\'s been built.</li>
            <li>Open K-Klock in substratum and build the clock that you want, don\'t worry about not being able to find any option for the left indicators!</li>
            <li>Reboot or restart SystemUI and watch as your network indicators move to the left.</li>
        </ol>

        <p>
            <small>If this guide has been unclear in any way, let me know so I can fix it</small>
        </p>

    ]]></string>

    <string name="qs_bg"><![CDATA[
        <style media=\"screen\" type=\"text/css\">
            body {
                color: ?android:attr/textColorPrimary ;
            }
            a:link {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
            a:visited {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
        </style>

        <h3><center><u>Custom Qs Background Guide</u></center></h3>

        <p>
              Special thanks to @ungeeked for making this mod in the first place.
              I have just ported it to K-Klock so I will be basing this guide off of
              <a href="https://forum.xda-developers.com/oneplus-3/themes/mod-add-custom-background-to-qs-panel-t3576949">this Thread.</a>

        </p>

        <ul>
            <li>You will be asked to select a png image when you select this option in K-Manager</li>
            <li>The recommended dimensions for customqs.png image are 1080*800 pixels or 1080x1000 pixels. You can use <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.appbasic.imageresizer&hl=en>Image Resizer </a> for this.</li>
            <li>You can use snapseed or picsart to crop your images and jpg2png.com to convert your jpgs to pngs</li>
            <li>Remember to only use pngs. jpgs are not supported</li>
            <li>After building K-Klock simply install the SystemUI Headers overlay and you\'re done!</li>
            <li><strong>Disclaimer: This doesn\'t work on Oos atm, I\'m hoping that that\'ll change by Oreo</strong></li>

        </ul>

        <p>
            If you want to select a new image just toggle the Qs Background Option in K-Manager and it will ask you for an image.
        </p>

        <p>
            <small>If this guide has been unclear in any way, let me know so I can fix it</small>
        </p>

    ]]></string>

    <string name="general_faq"><![CDATA[
        <style media=\"screen\" type=\"text/css\">
            body {
                color: ?android:attr/textColorPrimary ;
            }
            a:link {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
            a:visited {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
        </style>

        <h3><center><u>FAQ\'s</u></center></h3>

    <ul>
        <li><section>
            <h3>I\'ve installed K-Manager but I can\'t find anything in substratum???</h3>
            <p>Make sure that you have built of the K-Klock apk! If you haven\'t, tap the yellow build button at the bottom right corner of K-Manager and install K-Klock when prompted.</p>
        </section></li>

<li>        <section>
            <h3>How do I move the my custom clock format to the right/left/center of the statusbar?</h3>
            <p>
                Open K-Klock in substratum and tap on the \'Clock Style\' option. Here you can select the clock position.<br/>
                You can also choose whether to keep the clock visible on your lockscreen or not!
            </p>
            <p>
                <i>The White-Grey option lets you install a dynamically changing clock just like the stock one.</i>
            </p>

        </section></li>

   <li>     <section>
            <h3>I want to add a custom format but it\'s not working?</h3>
            <p>
                I\'d recommend reading this <a href="https://forum.xda-developers.com/showthread.php?t=2713812">XDA Thread</a> first.
                After that, ask in my thread and I\'ll help you out!
            </p>
        </section></li>

        </ul>

    ]]></string>

    <string name="about_other_roms"><![CDATA[
        <style media=\"screen\" type=\"text/css\">
            body {
                color: ?android:attr/textColorPrimary ;
            }
            a:link {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
            a:visited {
                color: ?android:attr/colorAccent ;
            }
        </style>

        <h3><center><u>FAQ\'s</u></Other Roms Option></h3>

        <article>
            <h3>About other Roms</h3>
            <ul>
                <li>This option modifies the xml files necessary to create K-Klock on the go</li>
                <li>Unfortunately, these xml files are different for each Rom
                <li>Since I don\'t have the xml files from every Rom, you\'ll have to provide these yourself</li>
                <li>Below is an easy step-by-step guide that anyone should be able to follow</li>

            </ul>

        </article>

        <article>
            <h3>How to make the Other Roms option work</h3>
            <ol>
                <li>
                <section>
                    <h3>Download an apk decompiler</h3>
                    <p>
                        I would recommend <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gmail.heagoo.apkeditor&hl=en">Apk Editor</a>
                        It\'s faster than using a Pc for everything.
                    </p>
                </section>
                </li>

                <li>
                    <section>
                        <h3>Find and decompile your Roms SystemUI.apk</h3>
                        <p>
                            If you\'re not rooted you\'re going to need a Pc for this part. Make sure you have Adb Drivers installed on your Pc (Google how).
                            Open up a command terminal and type: </p>
                            <ol><li>adb pull /system/priv-app/SystemUI/SystemUI.apk</li>
                            <li>adb push SystemUI.apk /sdcard/</li></ol>
                            <p>

                             You should now have a file called SystemUI.apk in your internal storage.
                        </p>
                        <p>
                            Now for the <strong>decompiling! </strong>
                            Open up Apk Editor.
                            <ul>
                                <li><em>If you\'re rooted</em> select an Apk from App. Then tap the three dots at the top to find system apps.
                                 Now search for System UI and decompile with Full Edit.</li>
                                <li><em>If you aren\'t rooted</em> select Apk from File. Then search System UI and you\'ll find the file that you adb\'d before.
                                Decompile this with Full Edit.
                            </ul>
                        </p>
                        <p>Now select Files at the bottom of Apk Editor</p>
                      </section>
                </li>
                <li>
                <section>
                    <h3>Exctracting the files</h3>
                    <p>
                        Now navigate to res -> layout and select the following three xml\'s:
                    </p>
                    <ul>
                        <li>keyguard_status_bar.xml</li>
                        <li>status_bar.xml</li>
                        <li>system_icons.xml</li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>
                        Then use the Extract option at the bottom to extract the xmls to K-Klock/userInput (case-sensitive).
                    </p>
                </section>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <h3>Chill Out!</h3>
                    <p>
                        Now open K-Manager and start changing stuff!
                        You won\'t have to repeat this process unless those files are deleted.
                    </p>
                </li>

            </ol>

            <small>I have tried to make this guide as clear as possible but if you haveany ideas on how to improve it, Let me know</small>

        </article>

    ]]></string>



</resources>